Guide to the Yale School of Drama Audio-Visual Recordings
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Audiovisual recordings, 1927-1996; Accession 2009-A-067
  - Winterfest seminars
    - Season VI.
      - Kondoleon, Harry, Wendy Wasserstein, and Thomas Balse (mod.), "How I Got That Story", 1986 February 1; audiocassette (Box 96)
      - Guare, John and Gregory Mosher, "Bringing Stories to Life", 1986 February 1; 2 (Box 96–97)
    - Season XII.
      - Seminar #2, 1992 February 8; audiocassette (Box 98)
      - Seminar #3, "New Spaces", 1992; audiocassette (Box 99)
  - Yale School of Drama Faculty and Buildings, Costume Shop, 1927; videotape (VHS) (Box 108)
  - Non-Yale audiocassettes
    - The Art of Ruth Draper [commercially-produced], 1980; audiocassette (Box 110)
    - Elvira, Mistress of the Dark, Fright Sound Tape [commercially-produced], 1987; audiocassette (Box 111)
    - Keating, Keith
      - Shakespeares' Comedies, Vol. I: "Shakespeare: Poet-Dramatist [commercially-produced], 1985; audiocassette (Box 112)
      - Shakespeare's Tragedies
        - Vol. VI: "From Verona to Denmark: A Poetic Transition [commercially-produced], 1985; audiocassette (Box 113)
        - Vol. X: "Shakespeare: Text and Subtext [commercially-produced], 1985; audiocassette (Box 114)
        - Vol. XIV: "The Way It Came Together [commercially-produced], 1985; audiocassette (Box 115)
- Videorecordings, 2007-2009; Accession 2010-A-032
  The materials are open for research.
  - SP2: Dramatis personnae, G. Rodriguez-Risco, Fall 2007; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 1U)
  - 2YAP: A Month in the Country, Fall 2007; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy (act 1), optical disk (DVD) (Box 2Ua)
    - Use copy (act 2), optical disk (DVD) (Box 2Ub)
  - 2YAP: Three Sisters, 2008; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy (act 1), optical disk (DVD) (Box 3Ua)
    - Use copy (act 2), optical disk (DVD) (Box 3Ub)
  - YSD2: The Robbers, 2008; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy (act 1), optical disk (DVD) (Box 4Ua)
    - Use copy (act 2), optical disk (DVD) (Box 4Ub)
  - YSD3: Jelly's Last Jam, 2009 February; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy (act 1), optical disk (DVD) (Box 5Ua)
    - Use copy (act 2), optical disk (DVD) (Box 5Ub)
  - 3YAP: Commedia: Even Maybe Tammy…, 2009; computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, optical disk (DVD) (Box 6U)
- Yale Institute for Music audio and video recordings, 2009; Accession 2010-A-037
  - Invisible Cities, 2009
    - Video recording, 2 (Box 1–2)
    - Audio recording
      - Use copy, compact disc (Audio CD) (Box 3U)
  - Pop!, 2009
    - Video recording, 2 (Box 4–5)
    - Audio recording
      - Use copy, 2 compact discs (Audio CD) (Box 6U–7U)
  - Sam I Was, 2009
    - Video recording, 3 (Box 8–10)
    - Audio recording
      - Use copy, 2 compact discs (Audio CD) (Box 11U–12U)
- Videorecordings, 2009-2010; Accession 2011-A-001
  - YSD4: the things are against us, computer files (DVD-Video)
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 1U)
  - YSD4: elijah part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 2U)
  - YSD4: elijah part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 3U)
  - YSD4: Every Other Hamlet In The Universe part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 4U)
  - YSD4: Every Other Hamlet In The Universe part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 5U)
  - SRP1: Macbeth, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 6U)
  - SRP2: Othello, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 7U)
  - SRP3: Midsummer Night's Dream part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 8U)
  - SRP3: Midsummer Night's Dream part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 9U)
  - SP1: The Droll, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 10U)
  - SP2: House of Cards, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 11U)
  - SP3: Good Goods, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 12U)
  - YSD1: Phedre, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 13U)
  - YSD2: La Ronde part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 14U)
  - YSD2: La Ronde part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 15U)
  - YSD3: Orlando part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 16U)
  - YSD3: Orlando part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 17U)
  - Commedia Project 2010, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 18U)
  - SPR: Homebody/Kabul part 1, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 19U)
  - SPR: Homebody/Kabul part 2, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 20U)
  - SPR: Homebody/Kabul part 3, computer files (DVD-Video)
    - Use copy, 2009-2010; optical disc (DVD) (Box 21U)
- Audiovisual recordings of plays and productions, 2010-2012; Accession 2013-A-001
  The materials are open for research. Duplication of media is prohibited to all non-authorized requestors.
  - 2010-2011 Season
    - Eurydice, 2010 October 26-30; 1 (Box 1)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire, 2010 December 10-16; 1 (Box 2)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 2U)
    - Jib, 2011 January 22-28; 1 (Box 3)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 3U)
    - Blacktop Sky, Undated; 1 (Box 4)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 4U)
    - Passing, Undated; 1 (Box 5)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 5U)
    - Tall Girls, Undated; 1 (Box 6)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 6U)
    - Uncle Vanya, 2010 October 7-9; 1 (Box 7)
      Second Year Acting Project
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 7U)
    - Ruzante, 2011 January 26-28; 1 (Box 8)
      Third Year Acting Project
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 8U)
    - The Taming of the Shrew, Undated; 1 (Box 9)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 9U)
    - Twelfth Night, Undated; 1 (Box 10)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 10U)
    - Tall Skinny Cruel Cruel Boys, 2010 November 11-13; 1 (Box 11)
      Studio Production 2
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 11U)
    - Arcadia, Undated; 1 (Box 12)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 12U)
  - 2011-2012 Season
    - Carlotta Festival of New Plays
      - The Bachelors, 2012 May 4-12; 1 (Box 13)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 13U)
      - Petty Harbour, 2012 May 4-12; 1 (Box 14)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 14U)
      - Fox Play, 2012 May 4-12; 1 (Box 15)
        - Use copy, 1 (Box 15U)
    - The Really Big Fat Drama Show, 2012 January 30-February 1; 1 (Box 16)
      3rd Year Acting Project
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 16U)
    - Angels in America Part Two - Perestroika 1 of 2, Undated; 1 (Box 17)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 17U)
    - Angels in America Part Two - Perestroika 2 of 2, Undated; 1 (Box 18)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 18U)
    - Fen, 2012 April 19-21; 1 (Box 19)
      Spring Project
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 19U)
    - Doctor Fausts Lights the Lights, 2011; 1 (Box 20)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 20U)
    - Cymbeline Act I, Undated; 1 (Box 21)
      Directed by Louisa Proske
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 21U)
    - Cymbeline Act II, Undated; 1 (Box 22)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 22U)
    - The Seagull, 2012 January 24-28; 1 (Box 23)
      YSD Series 3
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 23U)
    - Julius Caesar, 2012 February 9-11; 1 (Box 24)
      Shakespeare Repretory Project 1
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 24U)
    - Antony and Cleopatra, 2012 March 8-10; 1 (Box 25)
      Shakespeare Repertory Project 2
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 25U)
    - The Most Lamentable Roman Tragedy of Titus Andronicus, 2012 April 4-7; 1 (Box 26)
      Shakespeare Repertory Project 3
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 26U)
    - Rodeo, 2011; 1 (Box 27)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 27U)
    - Outlaw Jean, 2011 November 17-19; 1 (Box 28)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 28U)
    - Duck on a Bike, 2011 December 1-3; 1 (Box 29)
      Studio Production 3
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 29U)
- Audiovisual recordings of plays and productions, 2012-2013; Accession 2014-A-042
  - Production 1: Iphigenia Among the Stars, 2012 October; 1 (Box 1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 1U)
  - Production 2: Sunday in the Park with George, 2012 December; 1 (Box 2)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 2U)
  - Production 3: Cloud Nine, 2013 January; 1 (Box 3)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 3U)
  - Production 4: Carlotta Festival of Plays
    - House Beast, 2013 May; 1 (Box 4)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 4U)
    - Sagittarius Ponderosa, 2013 May; 1 (Box 5)
      - Use copy, 1
        Use copy deaccessioned.
    - Lottie Late in the Afternoon, 2013 May; 1 (Box 6)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 6U)
  - Third-year acting project: All Which Way and That, 2013 February; 1 (Box 7)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 7U)
  - Second-year acting project: Vieux Carré, 2012 October; 1 (Box 8)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 8U)
  - Shakespeare Repertory project 1: Two Gentlemen of Verona, 2013 February; 1 (Box 9)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 9U)
  - Shakespeare Repertory project 2: Romeo and Juliet, 2013 March; 1 (Box 10)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 10U)
  - Shakespeare Repertory project 3: King Richard II, 2013 April; 1 (Box 11)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 11U)
  - Studio series 1: Blueberry Toast, 2012 November; 1 (Box 12)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 12U)
  - Studio series 2: No More Sad Things, 2012 November; 1 (Box 13)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 13U)
  - Studio series 3: Mexico Play (A Farmer's Almanac), 2012 November; 1 (Box 14)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 14U)
  - Spring project 1: Wintertime, 2013 April; 1 (Box 15)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 15U)